Therefore, the development of vascular trajectories.
血管経路の発達についてです。
First, the specific image we have of the circulatory system,
まず、私たちが特に持っている循環器系のイメージですが、
you have a system that originates from the heart, which we call the arterial system,
心臓から出ていくシステムがあり、それを動脈系と呼びます。
and then we are told, it returns to the heart via the
そして、それは心臓に、
venous system.
静脈系によって戻ると言われます。
I agree that it originates and returns.
それが出て、戻ってくることには同意します。
There are in fact three different venous systems.
実際には、3つの異なる静脈系が存在します。
One system like this,
このようなシステムが一つ、
A system that is solely related to the, let's say, vertebral system.
いわゆる脊椎系にのみ関係するシステムが一つ。
And thirdly, there is a portal system.
そして第三に、門脈系があります。
This will drain the entire ectodermal system.
これは、外胚葉系全体を排液します。
This will drain the entire mesodermal system.
これは、中胚葉系全体を排液します。
This will drain the entire endodermal system.
これは、内胚葉系全体を排液します。
You see, indeed, okay, it comes here.
ご覧の通り、確かに、それはここに来ます。
But it can reverse direction.
しかし、それは向きを変えることができます。
It can take other trajectories depending
それは、
on the pressures and depressions within the body.
体内の圧と陰圧に応じて、他の経路を取ることができます。
You see, suddenly, someone with an overloaded portal system,
例えば、門脈系が過負荷になっている人がいるとします。
if it cannot return, it will take another route,
もしそれが戻ることができない場合、別の経路を取ります。
it will take a caval return system with very specific fields
非常に特定の領域を持つ大静脈系への還流経路を取るでしょう。
which are the diaphragmatic exchange zones.
それは横隔膜の交換領域です。
So that means that pressures can...
つまり、圧力は...
re-equilibrate. So, not only
再び均衡を保つことができます。つまり、単に
it does not make a single loop like this,
このように一周するだけではなく、
but it does this
このように動き、
and it can take other
そして他の
pathways. There is like an intelligence
経路を再び取ることができます。このシステムには、ある種の知性が
within this system
存在し、
to go towards the home
心臓という「家」へ向かうために、
of the heart. It certainly departs
それは確かに心臓から出発します。
from the heart, it indeed returns to the heart,
心臓から、それは確かに心臓に戻ります。
but in your venous system,
しかし、あなたの静脈系では、
the circulatory system,
循環器系について、
the vision we have of it dates back to the 17th
私たちが持っている見解は17世紀に遡ります。
century. This means that now,
世紀です。それは今や、
it has been renovated, the first ones
刷新され、最初に
to study this are Mr. Erlia and Mr. Batson, and that it's not the same return. My
それを研究したのはエルリア氏とバトソン氏であり、同じ還流ではないということです。私の
reaction was, yes, but I was told that in the veins there were valves that
反応は「はい、しかし私は、静脈には弁があり、
prevented backflow. Well, in fact, that's only in the large veins, but not at all in
逆流を防ぐと説明されました」。しかし実際には、それは大きな静脈にのみ存在し、全く存在しないのは
the entire
全ての
network. There are very few small valves like that. Because we will study the
ネットワークです。実際には、そのような小さな弁は非常に少ないのです。なぜなら、私たちは
cardinal veins which will become subcardinal and supracardinal.
主静脈、それが亜主静脈および上主静脈となるものを研究するからです。
You have another system
もう一つのシステムがあります。
called the vitelline system, related to the liver. And then a third level,
肝臓に関連する卵黄静脈系と呼ばれるものです。そして第三のレベルは、
this will be
それは
the entire umbilical system, it will be the entire development of the venous system
全ての臍帯系であり、それは静脈系の全ての発生です。
that we
私たちが
will re-examine in the vertebral caval-portal system and that we will reintegrate into
椎骨-大静脈-門脈系で再検討し、そしてそれを
osteopathic practice. The entire cardinal system will modify so much
オステオパシーの実践に組み込むでしょう。全ての主静脈系は非常に大きく変化します。
that we will see
私たちは見るでしょう。
this in detail to form tissues, structures that will integrate both
それを詳細に、組織や構造を形成するために、それらは同時に統合されます。
into the structures you have unfolded.
構造の中に、そして展開されます。
and mesodermal. I have found a method where you can apply this in practice,
および中胚葉性です。私はそれを実践に適用できる方法を見つけました。
where I summarize
そこで私は要約します。
this ultimately. But one must have understood the meaning. Stases, changes
それを最終的に。しかし、その意味を理解している必要があります。鬱滞、変化、
in abdominal pressure,
腹腔内圧の、
etc. Like someone who comes with low back pain, it can be an overload of the portal system.
など。腰痛を訴えてくる人のように、それは門脈系の過負荷である可能性があります。
And so, the vertebral system must be cleared due to portal
したがって、過負荷によって椎骨系を再解放する必要があります。
overload. And this is where you have
門脈の。そして、そこであなたは
the entire mechanism of discopathies that will integrate.
椎間板症の全てのメカニズムが統合されるのです。
Any stasis will lead to acidity, even local, which will need
鬱滞はすべて、局所的な酸性をもたらし、それが解消される必要がある。
to be cleared.
解消するために。
We observe that it always follows the same pattern,
それが常に同一のスキームを用いることが観察される。
that when I have a sacral tumor, I almost always, metastatically,
仙骨に腫瘍がある場合、転移部位としてほぼ常に、
have left kidney, left lung, and brain involvement.
左腎、左肺、そして脳が見られる。
But we observe that there is always a consistent line.
しかし、常に同一のラインが存在することが観察される。
This means that in prostatic problems, it can manifest here.
これは、前立腺疾患においてもここに現れる可能性があることを意味する。
Furthermore, there is a continuity
さらに、連続性がある。
vascular between the vertebral sinuses and the sacral sinuses of the lesser
椎骨静脈洞と小骨盤の仙骨静脈洞との間の血管性の
pelvis.
連続性。
A blood draw taken from an arm here does not capture the entirety of a blood draw
ここで腕から行われた採血は、採血の全体を捉えるものではない。
that would be taken from a venous, arterial, or other system.
静脈系、動脈系、あるいはその他のシステムで採取されるような。